<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="1" />
    To add people to the database, navigate to the B1.church Admin dashboard.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Click on People in the left sidebar.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Click the Add Person button in the upper right corner.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Fill in the person's first name, last name, and email address, then click Add.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    The person's profile page will open. Click the edit pencil next to their name to edit their details.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Fill in additional information such as middle name, membership status, dates, address, and phone numbers.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Click on the Notes tab to add notes about the person.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Click on the Groups tab to view group memberships.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Click on the Attendance tab to view attendance records.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Click on the Donations tab to view donations.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Click on the Forms dropdown to select a form to fill out. These forms are user defined forms which you can build by following the forms tutorial. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Click Add Form to open the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Fill in the form details and click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Return to the Details tab and click Save to save the personal information.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    The details are now saved and visible on the profile.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    To add household members, click the edit pencil next to the household name.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    The household editor will open. Select the household role for the current person.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    After selecting the role, click Add to add another household member.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Type the person's name in the search box and click Search.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    When the person appears in the search results, click Select.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    Choose their household role and click Save to complete the household setup.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end"/>
    </speak>
</tutorial>
