<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Every B1 account comes with a website. To access your website builder, click Website in the left menu.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    This opens Website Pages where you can manage pages and content. Click Add Page at the top right.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Choose blank as the page type and name it Home.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Click Edit to start building your page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Click Page Settings to configure the title and URL.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Click the edit pencil.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Edit your page title and URL path here.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    For the home page, enter a forward slash with no text. Other pages use forward slash and page title. Click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Click Edit Content to begin adding content.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Click Add Content to open the elements panel.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Every page must begin with a Section. Choose Section to add a container.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Drag a Section onto your page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Click the section and switch to the CUSTOM tab.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    The CUSTOM tab controls colors for backgrounds, headings, text, and links.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Click the Background Type dropdown.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Choose Image to upload a background image.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    Or choose YouTube Video to add a video background.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Select Color and choose a background color.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Add an optional section ID for advanced styling.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    Click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    Your section displays with the custom background.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22" />
    Click MOBILE to preview mobile layout.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23" />
    Click Add Content again.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="24" />
    Choose from text, images, videos, cards, forms, and more.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="25" />
    Drag a Text element into your section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="26" />
    Type your text and customize formatting. Click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="27" />
    Drag an Image element below your text.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="28" />
    Click Select Photo.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="29" />
    Upload images or download stock photos. Select an image.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="30" />
    Click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="31" />
    Your section displays with text and image.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="32" />
    Preview your complete website.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial>
