<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    The Manage Appearance section allows you to configure global appearance options such as logo, colors, and fonts.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    You will see a preview of a website with your current styles.  Click any option on the right to get started.  We'll start with Color Palette.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    This is where you set the overall color theme for your site.  
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Click on any of the suggested pallets to choose a different scheme.
    The pairings show suggestions of how these colors can be used together.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    You can also set your own custom theme by double clicking on any of the five colors to manually set the color.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Slide the dial, use the dropper, set the RGB,
    <mark name="7" />
    Or use the toggle to set the value as hex.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Click Save and the preview will be updated with your choices.  Next we'll choose fonts.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    You can set global fonts for the headings and for the body text of your pages.  If you choose, you can still use additional fonts on specific elements.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Simply click on either font and you'll be able to choose from thousands of options provided by Google Fonts.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Search for a specific name or use the category filter to browse.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Choose a font and you can see how your pairing will look.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Click save and the preview site has also been updated.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    The CSS and Javascript section is an advanced option for those familiar with web development.  Add any code you wish to be included on your pages such as tracking scripts.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Finally the logo section allows you to brand your website and other features with your logo.  Click the pencil icon to edit.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    You'll need to provide two versions of your logo.  One for dark backgrounds and another for light backgrounds.  Simply click either to edit.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    You'll see an Upload button for providing the image.  Be sure it is on a transparent background.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    The site expects a 4 by 1 logo, so you will be given a cropping tool to ensure your logo is the appropriate shape by adding the necessary horizontal and vertical padding.  Adjust accordingly and click Update and Save.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial>