<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Thank you for signing up for B1.church. I’d like to show you a couple things to get you started with the programs. Using Google Chrome, Log in to B1.church. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Click sign in and enter your username and password.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    This will take you to the B1.church Admin dashboard. From here, you can manage your church’s data base, website, mobile app, lessons, and more.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Click on settings to set up your church’s information, administrative roles and other details.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Click on the edit pencil to set up your church information.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Back on the dashboard, click the question mark icon in the top right corner for help and tutorials.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Click view documentation.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    You will see a list of tutorials to help you get started with B1.church. A word of caution: because we are constantly updating and improving B1.church, some of these tutorials may be slightly out of date. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Now navigate back to the dashboard and click the arrow next to your profile picture and choose switch app
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Choose lessons.church
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    This will take you to Lessons.church, where you can manage your church’s online lessons and curriculum.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Switch back to B1.church by clicking the arrow next to your profile picture and choosing switch app again.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    You can now enter B1.church through the member portal or the admin portal. The member portal allows you to see how B1.church looks to your members, view your groups and manage your personal donations.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    This video is just a brief introduction to B1.church. Be sure to watch our tutorials to help you get the most out of these programs. Feel free to reach out to our support team with any questions you may have. Thanks for choosing B1.church!
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
    </speak>
</tutorial>