<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    To configure navigation links and sidebar tabs for your live stream, start from the Dashboard and click on "Sermons" in the left navigation menu.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    From the Sermons page, click on the "Live Stream Times" tab to access stream configuration.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    On the Live Stream Times page, click the "Settings" button to configure your streaming page options.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    In the Settings page, you'll see three sections: Navigation Links for header links, Sidebar Tabs for interactive elements, and External Resources. To add a navigation link, click the "Add" button in the Navigation Links section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Enter your link details. For this example, we're adding "Church Calendar" with the URL "/church-calendar". You can organize links under submenus by selecting a folder like "Home" from the Menu Organization section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    After selecting the Home folder, you'll see a confirmation that your link will be placed under that submenu. Click "Save Link" to add it.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    The new Church Calendar link now appears under the Home navigation link. To add a sidebar tab, click the "Add" button in the Sidebar Tabs section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Enter the tab name, select an icon, and choose the page type. For an External URL, enter the full web address. In this example, we're adding a "Womens Retreat Registration" tab with an external registration form URL. Click "Save Tab" when done.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Your streaming settings now show all configured navigation links and sidebar tabs. These will appear on your live streaming page for viewers to access additional resources and interactive features.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial>
