<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Surrounding your live stream video, you can have header links and sidebar nav items, with key resources.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    In the header, you can add simple links.  To do so, click the "Add" button in the Navigation Links section of the Stream Settings page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Enter the link text and url.  It can be any webpage, internal or external.  Click "Save" to add it to the header.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    The link will appear in the header of your streaming page and open in a new tab when clicked.  You can add as many links as you need.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Sidebar tabs appear in the right column of your streaming page and are ways for the user to interact on the page.  To add a new tab, click the "Add" button in the Sidebar Tabs section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Give your tab a name and click the icon drop down and search for a suitable icon.  An intuitive icon is especially important for mobile users.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    For the page type, there are four options:
    External Url - Allows you to embed any webpage from any site into a tab.
    Page - Allows you to create a new custom page with text, images, and links.
    Chat - Allows viewers of the stream to chat with each other.
    Prayer - Allows viewers to start a private chat with a prayer team member.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    We will choose Chat and click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    This will enable a new chat tab on your streaming page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    We'll also add an external page tab for sermon notes, and a prayer request tab.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Before we can add a page tab, we need to first create a new page by clicking the plus icon in the Pages section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Give it a name and url and click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Click on the page to add content.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    See the website builder tutorial for details on how to add content to a page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Now you can add your page as a sidebar tab, by clicking "Add" in the Sidebar Tabs section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Select Page as the page type and choose the page you just created.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    Our streaming page now has tabs for sermon notes...
    <break time="0.3s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    chat...
    <break time="0.3s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    prayer requests...
    <break time="0.3s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    and the offering report...
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial>