<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Let's set up check-in for your church. Navigate to the B1 Dashboard, click on People in the left sidebar.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Search for the person you'd like to add. If they're not found, you can add them as a new person by filling out the form below.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Enter their first name, last name, and email address, then click Add.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    You'll be taken to their profile page. Click the edit pencil next to their name to add more details.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Fill in any additional information you have, such as address, phone numbers, and birth date, then click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    To add family members, click the edit pencil in the Household section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Click the Add button to add family members to this household.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Next, click on Attendance in the top navigation to set up your services.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Click the plus icon in the top right to add a new campus.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Enter the name of your campus and click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Now click Add Service under your new campus to create a service.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Enter the service name and click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Click Add Service Time to add the time for this service.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Enter the service time and click Save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Now click on Groups in the top navigation to create groups for check-in.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Click the Add Group button to create a new group.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    Select an existing category or choose Add New to create a new category.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Enter the category name and group name, then click Add.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Click on the group you just created to configure it for check-in.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    Click the edit pencil to modify the group settings.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    Configure your attendance settings. Set Track Attendance to Yes to track who attends. Set Parent Pickup and Print Nametag to Yes if you want to print kid and parent tags at check-in.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22" />
    Select any labels that apply to this group, then choose a service time from the dropdown.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23" />
    Click Add to include the service time, then click Save. Your group is now ready for check-in. For more detailed information on setting up groups and adding people to groups see the Groups Setup tutorial.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial>
