<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1"/>
    Welcome to the Chums Automations tutorial. Automations help you streamline your church's workflows by automatically performing tasks based on specific triggers.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2"/>
    To get started with automations, navigate to the Chums dashboard and click on the Settings icon.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3"/>
    In the Settings menu, find and click on Automations.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4"/>
    You'll see a list of your existing automations. To create a new one, click the Add Automation button in the top right corner.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5"/>
    First, give your automation a descriptive name. This helps you identify its purpose later.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6"/>
    Next, choose a trigger. Triggers are events that start your automation, such as when someone joins a group or when a task is completed.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7"/>
    After selecting a trigger, you'll need to configure its specific settings. For example, if you chose "Person joins group" as your trigger, you'll need to select which group.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8"/>
    Now, add the actions that should occur when the trigger happens. Click Add Action to see the available options.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9"/>
    Common actions include sending an email, creating a task, or adding a person to a group. Select the action you want to perform.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10"/>
    Configure the details of your chosen action. For example, if you're sending an email, you'll need to write the subject and message.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11"/>
    You can add multiple actions to a single automation. They will execute in the order you add them.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12"/>
    Before saving, review your automation settings to ensure everything is configured correctly.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13"/>
    Click Save to activate your automation. It will now run automatically whenever the trigger conditions are met.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14"/>
    To manage existing automations, you can edit, pause, or delete them from the main automations list.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15"/>
    You can also view the history of your automations to see when they've been triggered and what actions were taken.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end"/>
  </speak>
</tutorial> 