<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Once you've added a section you can add elements to it.  Click the Plus icon to add a new element.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Regardless of the element type, simply drag it into a section...
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    And drop it on any of the green boxes.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    You will be prompted to customize the element.  For text simply set the alignment...
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Enter your text...
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    And use the editor controls to adjust the appearance.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    The element will appear on the page.  Double click it to edit.  Or drag and drop it to move.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Let's look at some other element types.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    "Text with Photo" is a common type for adding an image surrounded by text.
    Click Select Photo to get started.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    You can select from photos you've uploaded before in the gallery...
    <break time="0.3s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Upload a new photo...
    <break time="0.3s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Or select a stock photo.
    <break time="0.3s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Use the search feature to find a relevant photo.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Give your photo a label, set where the photo appears in relation to the text, your text alignment, and enter your text.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Click Save and the page will be updated with your text with photo.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Adding a simple photo is similar.  Click Select Photo...
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    This time note the aspect ratio drop down.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    This will allow you to select images that conform to a specific shape.  Very useful for ensuring consistency.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Give the photo a label, and if you wish to have it be a link, provide the url and click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    The image will be inserted, spanning the whole width.  See the video on Rows if you do not wish the image to be so wide.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial>