<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Navigate to the Chums dashboard
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Go to settings
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Choose Manage
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Click the edit pencil in the top right corner
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Navigate down to the Giving section and choose Stripe in the Provider box
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Go back to your Stripe account and copy your Public and Secret Key and paste them here
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    The rates are set at the default rate for Stripe. You can negotiate with Stripe and sometimes get these rates reduced. To apply for a nonprofit discount with Stripe, you'll need to confirm your 501(c)(3) status with Stripe and provide proof that at least 80% of your payment volume will be tax-deductible donations. You can then email Stripe nonprofit@stripe.com with your EIN, primary email address associated with your Stripe account, and confirmation of your nonprofit status.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Your donation landing page URL will be:
    yoursubdomian.b1.church/donation-landing for example: https://ironwood.b1.church/donation-landing.
    Now you can copy and paste or link your domain wherever you want to take donations.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    When you are finished click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Now let's go to B1 and set up a donation page on your website. Go to the manager drop down in the top right corner and choose switch app.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Choose B1.Church
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" /> 
    Once in B1 choose Admin Portal under your name.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    On the left side click on the arrow next to Mobile App and choose Website.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    An auto generated page is available to use as you design your website and mobile app. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    You can customize this page by clicking on it a converting it to a custom page.
    <break time="2s "/>
    <mark name="end" />
    </speak>
</tutorial>
