<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Let's learn how to add lessons in Lessons.Church as an admin.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    First, go to Lessons.Church and click on login.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Enter your credentials and click sign in.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Select your organization.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Click your name or the organization's name at the top right.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Select Admin.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Click the plus sign on the program you want to work on.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    To add a new program, use the plus sign in the top right.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    To add a new study in an existing program, click the plus study button.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Set whether the study should be live. Usually set to no initially for review.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Add a numerical value for the study's order.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Enter the study name.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Create a slug for the URL - no caps or spaces allowed.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Add a one-sentence description.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    You can add a longer description here.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    If you have a YouTube video, enter the embedded link.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    Add a series graphic - this is required. Click anywhere in the gray box.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Click Upload and choose your image.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Adjust the image using the corner handles.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    Click Update and then Save before leaving the page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    To create a lesson, click the lesson button under the study.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22" />
    Set whether the lesson should be live - usually no initially.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23" />
    Add a numerical value for the lesson's order.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="24" />
    Enter the lesson name, typically the lesson number.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="25" />
    Create a slug for the URL - no caps or spaces.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="26" />
    Add a longer description for the lesson.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="27" />
    If you have a YouTube video, enter the embedded URL.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="28" />
    Add a lesson graphic following the same steps as the series graphic.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="29" />
    To add files, click on Files from the Study Level.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="30" />
    Click the plus sign to add a new bundle.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="31" />
    Name your bundle and click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="32" />
    Click plus Resource to add files to your bundle.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="33" />
    Enter a resource name and click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="34" />
    Click the arrow to open your bundle folder.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="35" />
    Click Add to add files to your resource.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="36" />
    You can add three types of files: Variants for download and player, Assets for player only, or Bulk Add Assets.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="37" />
    Choose your file and label the variant with its file type.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="38" />
    To create venues, click on Venues.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="39" />
    Click the plus button to add a new venue.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="40" />
    Enter the venue name and click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="41" />
    After creating Large and Small Group venues, click edit on the venue you want to modify.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="42" />
    Click the plus button to add a new section.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="43" />
    Select Create New.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="44" />
    Enter a section name and any material notes, then click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="45" />
    Add your first role, typically the presenter.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="46" />
    There are five action types: Say, Do, Play, Download, and Note.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="47" />
    Select the appropriate action and enter the material.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="48" />
    Finally, mark the Lesson and Study as live, then test everything on Lessons.Church.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial> 