<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Forms are a great feature of B1.church Admin and b1 church. You can build People forms for your data base or stand alone forms for your website or to link to. To begin, navigate to the B1.church Admin dashboard.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Go to settings
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Choose Forms
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Click on the plus sign in the top right corner.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Give the form a name. We’ll call this form “Baptism” it will be a custom field in our People file.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Choose “People” in the drop-down menu
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Be sure to click “Save”.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Now we will put the questions within the “Baptism” custom field
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Click on the plus sign in the top right corner to add a question
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Add a provider from the drop down menu. This is where you will choose the type of question you are asking.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Write a title. This is the question you are asking.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Add a description.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Don’t forget to click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    You can make as many questions as you like. In this example we will add the question of what date the person was baptized.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Note that the people forms do not have a link associated with them. The links are associated with the stand alone forms.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Go to your People files to look at the custom field you just made titled Baptism. Click on any name.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    You can see the custom field at the bottom of the file.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Click on Baptism and fill out the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Once the field is complete it will show up at the bottom of each file. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    Now let’s go back to Forms and make a stand alone form
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    This form will be for the Ladies Retreat
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22" />
    Choose Stand Alone for this form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23" />
    You can make the form Public or Restricted. The restricted mode allows you to choose who you want to allow to fill out the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="24" />
    You can set a time frame that the form will be available.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="25" />
    Choose a begin date and an end date.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="26" />
    Write a thank you note for people who fill out the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="27" />
    Don’t forget to hit save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="28" />
    Now click on the form to add questions to the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="29" />
    Add as many questions as you like
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="30" />
    If you want to take payments with this form choose payments under questions.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="31" />
    Be sure to save
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="32" />
    Now let’s look at Form Members to see who has access to see the completed forms and edit the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="33" />
    You can set Permission to Admin or View only, and turn on or off email notifications.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="34" />
    To add a person just search for someone and add them.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="35" />
    Now let’s go over to B1 to add this form to a webpage
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="36" />
    Click on your icon in the top right corner
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="37" />
    Choose Admin portal
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="38" />
    Choose Website
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="39" />
    Click the plus in the top right corner of pages to add a page or open and existing page to add the form.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="40" />
    Give your page a name
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="41" />
    Click on the edit pencil to edit the page.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="42" />
    Add a section
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="43" />
    Choose the Form element
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="44" />
    From the drop down menu choose the form you want to use. In this case we will add the Ladies Retreat Registration 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="45" />
    Be sure to save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="46" />
    Use the text element to make a title above the form
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="47" />
    Your form is now ready to use.
    <mark name="end"/>
    </speak>
</tutorial>
