<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Displaying song lyrics is one of the main functions of FreeShow. Let's explore how to add a song and customize it to fit your needs.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    To quickly add a new song, right-click in the project window and select "New Show".
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    While you can manually enter lyrics by clicking "Quick Lyrics", most songs are already available. Let's use "Web Search" to find an existing song.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Select your preferred version of the song by clicking on it from the search results.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    You can now preview all the lyrics and make any necessary edits, add verses, or modify content. After reviewing the song, click on "Options".
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Adjust the display settings to your preference - for example, setting 4 lines per slide. Once you're satisfied, click "New Show" to create the song and add it to your library.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    In FreeShow, notice the Groups section. If you want to repeat a section, like adding Verse 1 at the end, simply click on it and it will append to the end of the song.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    To modify a verse, right-click on it and select "Edit".
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    When editing a verse, remember that changes will apply to every instance of that verse in the show.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Notice how the edit appears in all instances of Verse 1. Next, click on "Toggle Global Groups".
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Global groups are useful for adding breaks or common parts to songs. Click "New Layout" to create an alternative arrangement for this song.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    In our second layout, "Default 2", if we don't want to include Verse 6, right-click on it and select "Remove Group".
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    You'll see that Verse 6 is now removed from Default 2 layout.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    However, Verse 6 remains in the original Default layout, making it easy to switch between different versions of the song for various bands or arrangements.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
    </speak>
    </tutorial>