<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    To set up tasks for your leaders, church members, or groups, navigate to the Chums Dashboard.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Then click the plus sign on the task bar on the right side of your screen.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Here is where you will fill out the information for your task. Since you are the one that is making the task, it is associated with you.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Click the assign to box and type in the name of a person or click on group and type the name of a group.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Hit search.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Select the person or add them if they are not in the database.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Now give the task a title.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Type in a note to the person the task is assigned to.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    You can now see the task that you assigned. If you need to edit the task, just click on it and edit.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Now I’ll log in as Terry Seven so you can see what the task notification looks like to the person receiving the task.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    I’m now logged in as Terry Seven.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    You can see the tasks assigned to me listed on the right side of your screen. You can also see these tasks on your mobile app.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Click on the task to see the details.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Once the task is completed, you can change the status from open to closed.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Choose closed.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    The task is now completed and closed.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    It no longer shows up on your Chums dashboard.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
    </speak>
</tutorial>