<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Let’s make a new group and set up the group calendar. Navigate to the B1.church Admin dashboard then to People. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    Choose Groups.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    Click Add Group in the top right corner to add a group.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Choose a category name or make a new category. Give your group a name. Click add.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Click on your group name
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Click the edit pencil
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Fill in as much information as you like
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Be sure to click save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    To add a person to the group type their name then click add.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    You can also add members by leaving the search bar blank and hitting search.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Choose a person to be the leader of the group. The leader of the group is the only person who can edit the calendar. Any group member can see a list of events and comment on them.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Navigate to the drop down menu at the top right of your screen
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Choose switch app
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Go to B1.church
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    On the left side of your screen choose groups
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Choose your group to edit the calendar. In this case Master's Men
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    Click calendar on the left hand side of the screen
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Click add an event
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Give the event a title
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    Write a short description of the event
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    Add a start time
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22" />
    And an end time
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23" />
    Click the recurring box if the event is recurring
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="24" />
    You can choose intervals so the event will recur every so many days. For instance if you put three in the interval box it will repeat every third day
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="25" />
    Or you can choose frequency by day, week or month
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="26" />
    This event will repeat every Saturday
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="27" />
    There are multiple ways to view the calendar, Month
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="28" />
    Week
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="29" />
    Day
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="30" />
    And agenda
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="31" />
    Click the event to see details. Members and leaders can start a conversation within the event and leaders can edit.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="32" />
    You can add your calendar to your google calendar (or any other calendar) by clicking subscribe. You can also make a curated calendar to add to your website. Follow the curated calendar tutorial below.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
    </speak>
</tutorial>
