<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    Let's walk through how to connect Lessons.Church to the B1 app.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    First, you'll need to register or login to your Lessons.Church account.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    If you haven't already, you'll need to register your church.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    Make at least one schedule. You can create as many schedules as you want with as many classrooms as you have.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    Now, click on your name and select "Switch App".
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    Next, click on Chums. You'll need to have access to Chums to complete this step. If you don't, please contact your Domain Admin.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    Click on Plans.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Click the plus icon to add a new ministry.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    Choose whatever name you would like and click Add.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    Now click on Teams.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Again, click the plus icon to make a new team.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    Click Add to create the team.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Click on the class you just created.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Now, add any teachers you want to view the lesson to this team.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    Remember to click the add icon to save your changes.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    Now, let's switch the app back to Lessons.Church.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    Click "Edit" on the class where you want to add the volunteer team.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Choose the volunteer team you just organized.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Make sure to hit "Save" to complete the setup. Remember, whenever you add a new teacher, you will need to add them to the team in Plans on the Chums app.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    To access B1 on your phone or tablet, you can download it from the Google Play Store or Apple App Store.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    Search for B1.church in your device's app store.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22" />
    Click Install to download the app.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23" />
    Find your church in the app.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="24" />
    Click on your church to complete the setup.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="25" />
    That's it! Your app will now update every week with the correct lessons from Lessons.Church.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="26" />
    To see all this content in a regular browser or to share with parents or teachers, click Subscribe in Lessons.Church to get all the links you need.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial> 