<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorial>
  <speak>
    <mark name="1"/>
    Let's set up plans in B1.church Admin. In the B1.church Admin dashboard go to serving in the drop-down menu of dashboard
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2"/>
    Click on add ministry
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3"/>
    Give your ministry a name.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4"/>
    Click add
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5"/>
    In this case, we named our ministry worship now click on worship
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6"/>
    Now create a team, click on the teams icon in the top right corner
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7"/>
    Click create team
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8"/>
    Now give your team a name
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9"/>
    And click add
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10"/>
    Click on your team name to add members
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11"/>
    Search your database by leaving the search field blank or typing in the name and add members to the team
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12"/>
    Add as many members as you like
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13"/>
    Now, navigate back to the Ministry called “Worship” 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14"/>
    Click on manage to add people to the ministry and set up group details
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15"/>
    Click search or type a persons name to add them to the worship group. Add everyone who you will want to message about what is happening with the group.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16"/>
    Add as many people as you like.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17"/>
    You can send a message to your group or download a list.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18"/>
    Click the edit pencil to edit group details
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19"/>
    Here you have the option to add a meeting time and location, description, group photo and any new labels you would like. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20"/>
    Be sure to click save
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21"/>
    Now, navigate back to the Ministry called “Worship” and click on it
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="22"/>
    Click on create plan type
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="23"/>
    Give the plan type a descriptive name 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="24"/>
    In this case we called our plan type “Sunday Worship”. Click on that.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="25"/>
    Begin by clicking create service plan
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="26"/>
    Give the plan a name, date and whether or not to include the service order. You also have the option to copy the form from a previous plan.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="27"/>
    Click save
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="28"/>
    Click on the name of your plan
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="29"/>
    Click add position to your team assignments
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="30"/>
    Change the category name from "Band" to whatever category you like
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="31"/>
    Give the position a name and choose the number of people needed to fill that position
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="32"/>
    Choose a volunteer group to get the people from. 
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="33"/>
    Add as many positions as needed, be sure to save.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="34"/>
    Click to plus to add a time for the service
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="35"/>
    Make sure the date is correct
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="36"/>
    And choose the needed team  
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="37"/>
    Be sure to save
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="38"/>
    Now, choose and notify the volunteers. You can write them a note to remind or encourage them.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="39"/>
    Click on “person needed”  to add a volunteer
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="40"/>
    Choose from the names listed on the right
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="41"/>
    Click notify volunteers. They will be notified through the B1 App or if they are not registered with B1 they will receive an e-mail.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
  </speak>
</tutorial> 