<tutorial>
    <speak>
    <mark name="1" />
    The people tab of Chums helps you track key information on your members and visitors.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="2" />
    By default, you get a list of the 25 most recent additions.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="3" />
    You can use the search.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="4" />
    To find specific people.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="5" />
    You can also use the advanced search functionality to find people based on specific criteria.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="6" />
    For example, if we want to find men to invite to join the men's ministry.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="7" />
    We can search for men.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="8" />
    Who are 18 or older.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="9" />
    And are not already in the men's ministry.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="10" />
    We can also customize the results to include.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="11" />
    Additional information such as age and marital status.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="12" />
    If you have added custom fields, you could also include those values. We will cover those in another video.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="13" />
    Results can be sorted by any column and all lists can be exported to a CSV file to use with Excel or other spreadsheet programs.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="14" />
    Click on a person's name to view details.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="15" />
    You will see an overview of their information with the option to edit next to their name.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="16" />
    If you have added custom fields, you can view and edit those as well.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="17" />
    At the top of member details, you will see a notes icon with click notes to add more. These notes are only visible to staff members who can view the person's details.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="18" />
    Depending on your access, you may see additional tabs to view their attendance, as well as donations and groups.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="19" />
    Below his profile, you will see members of Robert's household with the option to edit.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="20" />
    You can set Robert's role as head of the household.
    <break time="1s"/>
    <mark name="21" />
    And his daughter as his child.
    <break time="2s"/>
    <mark name="end" />
    </speak>
</tutorial>
